question_data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The Mann Co. Store from Team Fortress 2 has the slogan &quot;We hire mercenaries and get in fights&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Nutella is produced by the German company Ferrero.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In &quot;Sonic Adventure&quot;, you are able to transform into Super Sonic at will after completing the main story.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Bill Cipher in the show &quot;Gravity Falls&quot; is the good guy.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Adolf Hitler was a german soldier in World War I.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the original Star Wars trilogy, Alec Guinness provided the voice for Darth Vader.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Celebrities", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Marilyn Monroe was born on July 1, 1926.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Scatman John&#039;s real name was John Paul Larkin.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Vietnam&#039;s national flag is a red star in front of a yellow background.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In &quot;Space Station 13&quot;,  the station has a clown aboard it.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
